stumpsprom.com 2007-12-19

# Prom Decorations, Prom Favors, Prom 2008 – Stumps Prom and Party

### Site Security

> At Stumps Prom, your security is our number one concern. We are pleased to tell you about the measures we have taken to ensure your security. 
> 
> We have followed and surpassed all industry standards necessary for a secure site. We are a GeoTrust™ secure site. This means that all information sent to our site is encrypted and protected against disclosure to third parties. 

> Our servers use SSL (Secure Sockets Layer). This is an advanced technology that **encrypts all of the information you send us** (this includes all of your personal information such as your name, address, credit card number, etc.) so that it cannot be read as the information as it travels over the Internet. 
> 
> SSL works with Microsoft Internet Explorer (v. 3.0 and higher), Netscape Navigator (v. 2.0 and higher) and America Online (v. 3.0 and higher). 
> 
> To ensure that you are accessing our secure server to place your order, look at the bottom of your browser. You should see a closed lock or unbroken key icon (depending on your browser). If you see either of these icons, then SSL is active. 
> 
> #### Cookies
>
>> A "cookie" is a small text file that your browser keeps on your hard disk, and is very common on the Internet. They are a way for Stumps Prom to remember who you are. They also allow us to "remember" what you put in your shopping bag as you browse through our product selection. However, you can still browse our products and use many of our site features without cookies. 
>> 
>> To place an order on Stumps Prom, your browser does need to accept cookies. If you do not feel comfortable modifying your browser preference files, please feel free to e-mail us for assistance. 
>> 
>> To enable cookies in your browser.
>> 
>>   * For Internet Explorer Users: Choose TOOLS, then INTERNET OPTIONS, then SECURITY, then CUSTOM LEVEL, then scroll down to the COOKIES area and choose ENABLE. 
>>   * For Netscape Users: Choose EDIT, then PREFERENCES, then ADVANCED, then see COOKIES area and choose ACCEPT COOKIES. 
>> 

> 
> #### Fair Credit Billing Act
>
>> Under the Fair Credit Billing Act, your bank or credit card company cannot hold you responsible for more than $50 of any unauthorized or fraudulent charges on your credit card. In the event of any unauthorized use of your credit card, you are required to notify your credit card provider in accordance with the agreement you have with them. 
>> 
>> Please rest assured that shopping on Stumps Prom is safe and secure! You'll find the experience fun, easy and quick. 

### Privacy Policy

> > Revised April 2005
>> 
>> We want you to know that we respect your privacy and value you as a customer. To this end, we have initiated policies to ensure that your personal information is handled safely and responsibly.
>> 
>> Please note:
>> 
>>   * By visiting or using our website, you are accepting the policies described in this Privacy Policy.
>>   * If, at any time, we alter our Privacy Policy, we will post a notice on our website.
>> 

> 
> #### **Customer Information**
>
>> We receive and gather information (such as customer name, address, phone number, e-mail address, and, when necessary, credit card information) from customers for the following purposes:
>> 
>>   * To process orders
>>   * To improve customer shopping experiences
>>   * To communicate about our products and services
>>   * To fulfill catalog requests
>>   * To send Order and Shipping Confirmation E-mails
>>   * To contact customers about their order
>> 

> 
> #### **E-mails/Newsletters**
>
>> You may sign up to receive promotional e-mails and newsletters on our website to find out about current specials, offers, sales, and more. If at any time you wish to stop receiving these e-mails, you have the option to remove your name from our mailing list. At the bottom of each e-mail/newsletter, you can click on a link to unsubscribe and remove your name.
>> 
>> Please note: we will NOT sell, rent or share your e-mail address or password with a third party. We understand that this information is private and will handle it in a responsible manner.
> 
> #### **Mailing Information**
>
>> If you do not want to receive our catalog at any time, please let us know. Be sure to provide your exact name and address (as it appears on the catalog mailing label), or send us the actual mailing label from the catalog. Please allow 6-8 weeks for us to update our mailing lists.
>> 
>> Mail your request to:
>>
>>> Stumps Prom  
>  Attn: Customer Service  
>  P.O. Box 305  
>  South Whitley, IN 46787-0305
>>> 
>>> _E-mail your request to:_  
>>> 
>>> _Or call us at:_  
>  1-800-227-2789
>> 
>> We will occasionally share our customers’ mailing and other information with select companies that we feel might be of interest to you, but we will never share any personally identifiable information we collect from you without your consent. If you prefer that we do not share your name, simply mail or e-mail us your name and mailing address. Again, be sure to provide your exact name and address so that we may identify you correctly.
>> 
>> We may employ other companies to provide similar marketing services on our behalf. With our approval, these third parties may also place “cookies” for analysis purposes. These third-party companies will have access to the information needed to perform their functions but cannot use that information for any other purpose. These third-party companies will only have access to non-personal information about your visit or transaction, such as the URLS which lead you to and around our site, pages visited, the product(s) purchased, and the amount spent; these companies will not have access to information that will allow them to personally identify you.
>> 
>> To remove your name from mailing lists of other printed catalogs that belong to the Direct Marketing Association, write to:
>>
>>> Mail Preference Department  
>  Direct Marketing Association  
>  P.O. Box 9008  
>  Farmingdale, NY 11735-9008
> 
> ### Children's Online Privacy Protection
>
>> In compliance with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of 2000 (COPPA), we do not request any information from children under the age of 13. We require parental consent (via e-mail) on any information provided to us by children under the age of 13. We have provided links on our site to our Privacy Policy from all places where information can be gathered.
> 
> ### Questions or Concerns
>
>> If you at any time have questions, concerns, or need assistance with our Privacy Policy, please feel free to e-mail us at [Customer Service](mailto:csr@stumpsprom.com), call us toll free at 1-800-227-2789 or write to us at:
>>
>>> Stumps Prom  
>  Attn: Customer Service  
>  P.O. Box 305  
>  South Whitley, IN 46787-0305
